<NotepadPlus>
    <UserLang name="Arturo" ext="art">
        <Settings>
            <Global caseIgnored="no" />
            <TreatAsSymbol comment="no" commentLine="yes" />
            <Prefix words1="no" words2="no" words3="no" words4="no" />
        </Settings>
        <KeywordLists>
            <Keywords name="Delimiters">{&quot;0}&quot;0</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folder+">[</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Folder-">]</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Operators">( ) * : + &lt; = &gt; / '</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Comment">1 2 0;</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Words1">abs acos acosh acsec acsech actan actanh add after all and and angle any append arg args arity array as ascii asec asech asin asinh atan atan2 atanh attr attr attribute attributeLabel attrs average before benchmark binary blend block break builtins1 builtins2 call capitalize case ceil char chop clear close color combine conj contains continue copy cos cosh csec csech ctan ctanh cursor darken database date dec decode define delete desaturate deviation dictionary dictionary difference digest digits div do download drop dup else empty empty encode ensure env epsilon equal escape even every execute exists exit exp extend extract factors false false fdiv filter first flatten floating floor fold from function function gamma gcd get goto greater greaterOrEqual hash help hypot if if in inc indent index infinity info inline input insert inspect integer intersection invert is join key keys kurtosis label last leap less lessOrEqual let levenshtein lighten list literal ln log logical loop lower lower mail map match max maybe median min mod module mul nand nand neg negative new nor nor normalize not not notEqual now null null numeric odd open or or outdent pad panic path path pathLabel pause permissions permutate pi pop positive pow powerset powmod prefix prefix prime print prints product query random range read relative remove rename render repeat replace request return reverse round sample saturate script sec sech select serve set set shl shr shuffle sin sinh size skewness slice some sort sorted split sqrt squeeze stack standalone string strip sub subset suffix suffix sum superset switch symbol symbols symlink sys take tan tanh terminal to true true truncate try try type type union unique unless unless until unzip upper upper values var variance webview when while whitespace with word wordwrap write xnor xnor xor xor zero zip</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Words2">all? and? any? ascii? attr? attribute? attributeLabel? binary? block? char? contains? database? date? dictionary? empty? equal? even? every? exists? false? floating? function? greater? greaterOrEqual? if? in? inline? integer? is? key? label? leap? less? lessOrEqual? literal? logical? lower? nand? negative? nor? not? notEqual? null? numeric? odd? or? path? pathLabel? positive? prefix? prime? set? some? sorted? standalone? string? subset? suffix? superset? symbol? true? try? type? unless? upper? when? whitespace? word? xnor? xor? zero?</Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Words3"></Keywords>
            <Keywords name="Words4"></Keywords>
        </KeywordLists>
        <Styles>
            <WordsStyle name="DEFAULT" styleID="11" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="FOLDEROPEN" styleID="12" fgColor="FF0000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="FOLDERCLOSE" styleID="13" fgColor="FF0000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORD1" styleID="5" fgColor="0000B6" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORD2" styleID="6" fgColor="A000FF" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORD3" styleID="7" fgColor="008000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="KEYWORD4" styleID="8" fgColor="A000B6" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="COMMENT" styleID="1" fgColor="A0A0A0" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="COMMENT LINE" styleID="2" fgColor="C0C0C0" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="NUMBER" styleID="4" fgColor="B20000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="OPERATOR" styleID="10" fgColor="0000FF" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMINER1" styleID="14" fgColor="F08000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMINER2" styleID="15" fgColor="F08000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" />
            <WordsStyle name="DELIMINER3" styleID="16" fgColor="000000" bgColor="FFFFFF" fontName="" fontStyle="0" />
        </Styles>
    </UserLang>
</NotepadPlus>